freewarebb.com 2009-02-01

# Privacy Policy - Freeware Software Downloads

Advanced Member  

Group: Root Admin  
Posts: 141  
Joined: 18-October 07  
From: Scotland, UK  
Member No.: 2

Please note that ALL our staff are required to agree to uphold, and abide by the following privacy statement before being allowed to take up any position on our site. If you feel that any part of this statement hasn't been followed, please use the [Contact Us](http://www.freewarebb.com/index.php?autocom=contactform) form to let us know about the matter immediately.

 **Registration**  
Registration on our site is required purely to gain access to additional features and those who choose not to register can still gain access to our freeware downloads. This registration is purely to validate their identity as email confirmation from the visitor is required to complete the registration process. Once registration is complete, no further details are asked for.

 **Cookies**  
Cookies simply allow users to browse our site whilst certain information is then stored in a file on their PC which serves to aid the browsing experience. A typical example of this would be when someone logs in to our site as a member and doesn't want to have to enter their user-name and password on each visit. This information can be stored in a "cookie" and although there is no requirement for anyone to allow cookies, certain area's of our site may require that cookies be enabled on your PC to maximize the browsing experience. 

**Log Files**  
We use IP addresses to analyze trends, administer the site, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use.

 **Sharing**  
We will not share any information on any user other than for internal use by FreewareBB and it's staff. If we are required by law to provide information we will do so only by means of a warrent.

 **Links**  
This web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this Web site.

 **Security**  
FreewareBB take every reasonable precaution to secure our site and it's contents. User data is not readily available unless an Administrator of the site makes it available to key personnel and only then is it granted for specific purposes.

 **Site and Service Update**  
We may, from time to time, send members site and service announcement updates. Members are able to un-subscribe from service announcements, which contain important information about the site or it's features.

 **Notification of Changes**  
If we change this statement, we will immediately email our members to inform them of such and wherever possible place a notice to the effect on our site also.
